Hey everyone.
Today I would like to show you our new model that's called Gina Embedings V5 Omni.
There is a small variant and we also have a nano version of this which is much smaller.
And so what it can do is it can get text as input but also images, video, it can get text as input,
and any combination of these at any number of these and it creates a single embedding and this embeddings can be used
for clustering or for retrieval so it means all the documents you embed consist of combinations of
text image audio and video for instance products that has a text description or title and multiple images and you can
embed the whole product into a single vector and your search query can also contain multiple
attributes here's a small demo for our model so i have five data sets here each for one modality
and i can build some queries also with all the different modalities to search of these data sets
and just for fun let's search on the photos using audio and what other that even means
we can give it a try.
Meow, meow, meow.
So as you can see, our model is truly an omnimodal.
So many other models can only search either on text or on image and text or text and audio, these combinations.
But in our case, all these modalities come into a shared embedding space.
And this allows to have such cross-modalities.
modality search requests, which is quite nice.
Let's search for some rock music, for instance.
So this is the results we get on the photos.
And then these are the results we get on the audio.
You can think about many possible use cases.
For instance, here I search on our documents data set
and I uploaded an invoice to retrieve similar invoices
as results. So now let's talk about a bit more complex queries we can construct.
So what we can also do is, for instance, giving a drawing here of a car,
then retrieving some cars as response, and then we can adjust the query even further by adding more modalities.
And for instance, we can specify now white.
So now the red car is a bit downranked and we get more white cars as response.
And the additional attribute we specified here is not an additional filter
because there is no filter attribute in the result images.
It's really another input modality we add to the embedding model together with the car to retrieve these results.
And it might not work in any case, so you can maybe not combine everything with each other.
And there are a bit of experiments you have to do what works with each other.
But this shows, in principle, this is possible.
You can find it on Heminghamming Face and just give it a try and let us know.
So, come in.